vintagesynth.com 2017-06-06

# VINTAGE SYNTH EXPLORER | Vintage Synth Explorer

## VINTAGE SYNTH EXPLORER

  1. Home
  2. About
  3. Vintage synth explorer 

### Privacy Policy Statement

www.vintagesynth.com

www.vintagesynth.org

### General policy

Vintage Synth Explorer respects your privacy. The information that you provide us with, or that is gathered automatically helps us and third parties to monitor our service and provide you with the services that you have subscribed to. Please bear in mind that any personal information that you submit through forums, letters/emails for publication and the like may be collected by others. However, we do NOT sell your information to any outside parties. If you have any concerns, questions or comments please email the [Webmaster](mailto:webmaster@vintagesynth.com).

### Registration

Our site may require you to register with us. This is to allow access to extra services that we provide for you. The information is not used for sending you newsletters or promotions unless stated.

### Cookies

We use 'cookies' to track advertising information and website usage. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Certain features of the Synth Classifieds require that you accept cookies in order to work properly. On certain sites, or third party sites we may utilize cookies for other purposes such as order tracking in online shops or for targeting advertisements to particular types of visitor.

Generally, we use cookies for the following purposes: Advertising networks that serve ads onto the Synth Classifieds may use their own cookies. The Synth Forums may also collect IP addresses for system administration.

### How your information is used

The primary goal of the Vintage Synth Explorer in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience and to assist your navigation throughout the site.

### Who is collecting your information

When you are asked for personal information on the Vintage Synth Explorer, you are sharing that information with the Vintage Synth Explorer alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. However, some activities will, by their very nature, result in your personal information being revealed to other users of the Synth Forums. For example, when you enter personal information on the profile form, this information will generally be included in your posts or ads, unless specifically stated otherwise.

### Third party sites

Our site operates with third party sites (such as online shops). We may, on occasion, share non-personal aggregated information to these third parties.

### With whom your information may be shared

As a general rule, the Vintage Synth Explorer will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. The Vintage Synth Explorer may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service of the the Vintage Synth Explorer or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of the the Vintage Synth Explorer, other users of the the Vintage Synth Explorer, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. the Vintage Synth Explorer may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.

### What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information

If you choose not to provide personal information, you can still use some areas of the Synth Forums, but you will not be able to access areas or use features that require you to submit personal information, such as posting topics and ads. You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those services of the Synth Classifieds that require registration in order to participate. You can still use most of the features of the Synth Forums even if you do not accept cookies. The Vintage Synth Explorer does not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service.

### How you can access, update or delete your information

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may edit or delete your profile at any time by clicking on the appropriate link or graphic provided by the system.

### The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information

Other than the administrator of the Synth Forums or other authorized personnel of the the Vintage Synth Explorer, you are the only person who has access to your personal information. Your ads are password-protected to prevent unauthorized access. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. The Vintage Synth Explorer will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, the Vintage Synth Explorer cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

### How the Vintage Synth Explorer protects children's privacy

The Vintage Synth Explorer is a general audience web site. Children should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. The Vintage Synth Explorer does not share personal information about users under the age of 13 with third parties and we do not sell or rent personal information about any of our users, regardless of age. In addition, the Vintage Synth Explorer will not send any direct email offers to users who indicate they are under the age of 13.

### What else you should know about your online privacy

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example in ads that you post or through email - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

### Surveys

On occasion we may conduct online surveys. This is used to gauge our service, collect demographic information and other information that we may find useful. These surveys are optional. We may share non-personal, aggregated information with third parties.

### Security

While we strive to keep the information that you supply directly or indirectly secure please be aware that the Internet is not a fully secure medium.

### Usage of information

If requested we may submit your information to local or government authorities.

### Policy changes

By using our site you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware that our policy may change with time. Any changes to this policy will appear on this web page.
